<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on vansh&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on vansh&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chat as Primary Interface; And Why It&#39;s Not Enough</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2025-07-21-ai-ux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2025-07-21-ai-ux/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;millennials-and-the-magic-wand&#34;&gt;Millennials and the Magic Wand&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sam Altman - the YC guy? Before there was OpenAI, there was Loopt; before there were LLMs, there was ML; and before there was chat, there was the &lt;code&gt;magic wand&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2010s were a vibe, money was free and the jeans were skinny. The magic wand in a way accurately captured the mood of the decade. You&amp;rsquo;d digitize a niche, sprinkle a Bayes classifier, slap the wand label and raise a million dollar seed in the name of ML. Quick and lazy, and it worked until it didn&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety: Why your AI should have a Girlfriend</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2025-07-08-ai-safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2025-07-08-ai-safety/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A computer can never be held accountable; therefore, a computer must never make a management decision. — &lt;em&gt;IBM Training Manual, 1979&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I never took AI safety seriously. It always seemed beyond pay grade or reserved for activists, like nuclear energy or the middle east.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That changed earlier this year when I built a text-based query platform for a customer. To set the stage, we were dealing with over 4,000 unlabeled tables, a handful of APIs for schema retrieval, and notoriously poor naming conventions. Until then, executives depended entirely on a small IT team to manually generate reports.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disrupting the Arena (b2b saas)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2025-07-01-b2b-saas-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2025-07-01-b2b-saas-future/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the more things change, the more they stay the same - Jon Bon Jovi&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;B2B Saas is maybe the oldest profession out there. The pimp tracking his girls in the wild west was really just doing b2b saas with human as a controller. You scoff, but almost every succesfull YC startup was once a precocious founder with an excel sheet (see: vanta).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But modern business software runs on computers and boils down to 3 components:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
